<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Exercises><Exercise><Name>Iceberg Crunch</Name><Description>Lie on your back with your hands behind your head. Crunch your upper body up towards your knees while lifting your legs to a 45-degree angle. Lower back down and repeat.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>180000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>1380000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Lifeboat Lunges</Name><Description>Stand with your feet hip-width apart. Take a large step forward with your right foot, bending both knees to a 90-degree angle. Push off with your right foot and step back to the starting position. Repeat with the left foot.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12 (each leg)</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>1380000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>2580000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>S.O.S. Squats</Name><Description>Stand with your feet slightly wider than shoulder-width apart. Lower your body down into a squat position, keeping your knees behind your toes. Push through your heels to return to the starting position.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>2580000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>3780000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Rose's Reach-ups</Name><Description>Lie on your back with your legs extended and arms overhead. Lift your arms and upper body off the ground, reaching towards your toes. Lower back down and repeat.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>3780000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>4980000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Jack's Jumping Jacks</Name><Description>Stand with your feet together and arms by your sides. Jump your feet out to the sides while raising your arms above your head. Jump back to the starting position and repeat.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>20</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>4980000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>6180000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Marathon Planks</Name><Description>Get into a plank position with your elbows on the ground and legs extended. Hold the position, engaging your core and keeping your body in a straight line.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>30 seconds</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>6180000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>7380000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Sinking Ship Sit-ups</Name><Description>Lie on your back with your knees bent and feet flat on the ground. Sit up, reaching your hands towards your feet, then lower back down and repeat.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>20 seconds</Rest><TimestampStart>7380000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>8580000</TimestampEnd></Exercise></Exercises>
