<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Exercises><Exercise><Name>Rocket's Rocket Jumps</Name><Description>Jump as high as you can, landing with a soft bend in your knees. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10</Reps><Rest>10 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>3000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>123000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Groot's Growing Lunges</Name><Description>Take a big step forward with your right foot, bending both knees to create two 90-degree angles. Push off with your right foot and return to a standing position. Repeat on the other side for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>133000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>258000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Quill's Quick Sprints</Name><Description>Sprint in place, driving your knees up high and pumping your arms as fast as possible. Keep a quick pace for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>20</Reps><Rest>20 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>268000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>408000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Gamora's Galaxy Lunges</Name><Description>Perform alternating lunges, stepping forward with one leg and bending both knees to create two 90-degree angles. As you step back, raise your arms up and out to the sides like you're floating in space. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>418000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>543000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Drax's Dumbbell Punches</Name><Description>Hold two imaginary dumbbells, one in each hand. Punch forward with alternating arms, keeping your fists tight and engaging your core. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>553000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>693000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Mantis' Mindful Yoga Poses</Name><Description>Perform a series of yoga poses, including downward dog, warrior II, and tree pose. Hold each pose for 30 seconds and flow between them smoothly. Repeat for the designated number of sets.</Description><Sets>2</Sets><Reps>30 secs each pose</Reps><Rest>20 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>703000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>873000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Groot's Grab and Lifts</Name><Description>Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart. Squat down, reaching towards the ground as if you're grabbing an object. As you stand up, lift your arms overhead as if you're raising the object. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>903000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>1038000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Ego's Explosive Mountain Climbers</Name><Description>Assume a push-up position with your hands on the ground and your body in a straight line. Bring one knee towards your chest, then explosively switch legs, bringing the other knee towards your chest. Continue switching legs as fast as you can for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15 each leg</Reps><Rest>20 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>1048000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>1188000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Yondu's Yoyo Jumps</Name><Description>Jump up with both feet, bringing your knees towards your chest. Land softly and immediately jump back up. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10</Reps><Rest>10 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>3603000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>3723000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Gamora's Galactic Squats</Name><Description>Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart. Bend your knees and push your hips back to lower into a squat position. Push through your heels to return to a standing position. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>3733000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>3873000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Quill's Quick Push-Ups</Name><Description>Assume a push-up position with your hands on the ground and your body in a straight line. Lower your chest towards the ground by bending your elbows, then push back up to the starting position. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>3883000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>4023000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Rocket's Rotating Planks</Name><Description>Assume a plank position with your forearms on the ground and your body in a straight line. Rotate onto one side, lifting your arm towards the ceiling and opening up your chest. Return to the starting position and repeat on the other side. Alternate sides for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10 each side</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>4033000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>4173000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Gamora's Galaxy Hops</Name><Description>Stand with your feet hip-width apart. Jump to your right side, landing softly with a slight bend in your knees. Immediately jump to your left side and repeat. Continue hopping back and forth for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>20</Reps><Rest>20 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>4183000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>4323000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Drax's Dynamic Plank Taps</Name><Description>Assume a plank position with your hands on the ground and your body in a straight line. Reach your right hand towards your left shoulder, then return it to the ground. Repeat with your left hand reaching towards your right shoulder. Continue alternating for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12 each side</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>4333000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>4473000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Mantis' Mindful Meditation</Name><Description>Sit in a comfortable cross-legged position. Close your eyes and take slow, deep breaths, focusing on your breath entering and leaving your body. Clear your mind and relax for the designated amount of time.</Description><Sets>2</Sets><Reps>1 min</Reps><Rest>30 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>4483000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>4603000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Rocket's Reactive Jumps</Name><Description>Jump forward with both feet, landing with a soft bend in your knees. Immediately jump back to the starting position. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>5403000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>5538000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Quill's Quick Burpees</Name><Description>Start in a standing position. Drop down into a push-up position, perform a push-up, then jump back up to a standing position. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10</Reps><Rest>10 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>5548000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>5668000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Groot's Growth Squats</Name><Description>Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart. Bend your knees and push your hips back to lower into a squat position. As you stand up, raise your arms overhead and reach towards the sky. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>5678000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>5818000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Ego's Exploding Push-Ups</Name><Description>Assume a push-up position with your hands on the ground and your body in a straight line. As you push up, explode off the ground and clap your hands together before landing softly. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10</Reps><Rest>10 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>5828000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>5948000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Yondu's Yoyo Crunches</Name><Description>Lie on your back with your knees bent and your feet flat on the ground. Place your hands behind your head and lift your shoulders off the ground, crunching towards your knees. Lower back down and repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>6303000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>6438000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Gamora's Galaxy Leg Raises</Name><Description>Lie on your back with your legs extended. Lift both legs off the ground, keeping them straight, until they are perpendicular to the floor. Slowly lower them back down without touching the ground. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>6448000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>6588000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Drax's Double Crunches</Name><Description>Lie on your back with your knees bent and your feet flat on the ground. Place your hands behind your head and lift your shoulders off the ground, crunching towards your knees. At the same time, lift your hips off the ground, bringing your knees towards your chest. Lower back down and repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>6598000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>6738000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Mantis' Mindful Stretching</Name><Description>Perform a series of stretches to release tension in your muscles. Focus on your breath and hold each stretch for 30 seconds. Repeat for the designated number of sets.</Description><Sets>2</Sets><Reps>30 secs each stretch</Reps><Rest>20 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>6748000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>6898000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Gamora's Galactic Twists</Name><Description>Sit on the ground with your knees bent and your feet flat on the ground. Lean back slightly, engaging your core. Twist your torso to the right, tapping the ground with your fingertips, then twist to the left and repeat. Continue alternating for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15 each side</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>7203000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>7338000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Quill's Quick Side Planks</Name><Description>Assume a side plank position with your forearm on the ground and your body in a straight line. Hold this position for the designated amount of time on each side.</Description><Sets>2</Sets><Reps>30 secs each side</Reps><Rest>20 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>7348000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>7498000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Rocket's Reactive Side Steps</Name><Description>Stand with your feet hip-width apart. Step to the right with your right foot, then immediately step to the left with your left foot. Continue side-stepping for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>20</Reps><Rest>20 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>7508000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>7653000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Groot's Glute Bridges</Name><Description>Lie on your back with your knees bent and your feet flat on the ground. Lift your hips off the ground, squeezing your glutes at the top. Lower back down and repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>7663000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>7798000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Ego's Explosive Squat Jumps</Name><Description>Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart. Squat down, then explosively jump up, reaching towards the sky. Land softly and immediately go into the next squat jump. Repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>10</Reps><Rest>10 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>7808000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>7928000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Yondu's Yoyo Planks</Name><Description>Assume a plank position with your forearms on the ground and your body in a straight line. Hold this position for the designated amount of time.</Description><Sets>2</Sets><Reps>1 min</Reps><Rest>30 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>8103000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>8223000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Gamora's Galactic Calf Raises</Name><Description>Stand with your feet hip-width apart. Rise up onto your tiptoes, lifting your heels as high as possible. Lower back down and repeat for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>15</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>8233000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>8373000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Drax's Dynamic Shoulder Taps</Name><Description>Assume a push-up position with your hands on the ground and your body in a straight line. Lift one hand off the ground and tap the opposite shoulder. Return the hand to the ground and repeat with the other hand. Continue alternating for the designated number of reps.</Description><Sets>3</Sets><Reps>12 each side</Reps><Rest>15 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>8383000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>8523000</TimestampEnd></Exercise><Exercise><Name>Mantis' Mindful Cooling Down</Name><Description>Perform a series of gentle stretches to cool down your body and relax your muscles. Hold each stretch for 30 seconds and focus on deep, slow breathing.</Description><Sets>1</Sets><Reps>30 secs each stretch</Reps><Rest>60 secs</Rest><TimestampStart>8533000</TimestampStart><TimestampEnd>8999000</TimestampEnd></Exercise></Exercises>
